[{"question":" Which operator returns true if the two compared values are not equal?","options":[{"text":"`<>`","correct":false},{"text":"`~`","correct":false},{"text":"`==!`","correct":false},{"text":"`!==`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How is a forEach statement different from a for statement?","options":[{"text":"Only a for statement uses a callback function.","correct":false},{"text":"A for statement is generic, but a forEach statement can be used only with an array.","correct":true},{"text":"Only a forEach statement lets you specify your own iterator.","correct":false},{"text":"A forEach statement is generic, but a for statement can be used only with an array.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Review the code below. Which statement calls the addTax function and passes 50 as an argument?","options":[],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How would you use this function to find out how much tax should be paid on \\$50?","options":[{"text":"addTax = 50;","correct":false},{"text":"return addTax 50;","correct":false},{"text":"addTax(50);","correct":true},{"text":"addTax 50;","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nfunction addTax(total) {\n  return total * 1.05;\n}\n```"},{"question":" Which statement is the correct way to create a variable called rate and assign it the value 100?","options":[{"text":"let rate = 100;","correct":true},{"text":"let 100 = rate;","correct":false},{"text":"100 = let rate;","correct":false},{"text":"rate = 100;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which statement creates a new object using the Person constructor?","options":[],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which statement creates a new Person object called \"student\"?","options":[{"text":"var student = new Person();","correct":true},{"text":"var student = construct Person;","correct":false},{"text":"var student = Person();","correct":false},{"text":"var student = construct Person();","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When would the final statement in the code shown be logged to the console?","options":[{"text":"after 10 second","correct":false},{"text":"after results are received from the HTTP request","correct":false},{"text":"after 10000 seconds","correct":false},{"text":"immediately","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nlet modal = document.querySelector('#result');\nsetTimeout(function(){\n    modal.classList.remove('hidden);\n}, 10000);\nconsole.log('Results shown');\n```"},{"question":" When would 'results shown' be logged to the console?","options":[{"text":"immediately","correct":true},{"text":"after results are received from the HTTP request","correct":false},{"text":"after 10 second","correct":false},{"text":"after 10,000 seconds","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nlet modal = document.querySelector('#results');\nsetTimeout(function () {\n  modal.classList.remove('hidden');\n}, 10000);\n```"},{"question":" You've written the code shown to log a set of consecutive values, but it instead results in the value 5, 5, 5, and 5 being logged to the console. Which revised version of the code would result in the value 1, 2, 3 and 4 being logged?","options":[{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":true},{"text":"","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfor (var j = 1; j <= 4; j++) {\n  setTimeout(function () {\n    console.log(j);\n  }, j * 1000);\n}\n```"},{"question":" How does a function create a closure?","options":[{"text":"It reloads the document whenever the value changes.","correct":false},{"text":"It returns a reference to a variable in its parent scope.","correct":true},{"text":"It completes execution without returning.","correct":false},{"text":"It copies a local variable to the global scope.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement creates a new function called discountPrice?","options":[{"text":"","correct":true},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\ndiscountPrice = function (price) {\n  return price * 0.85;\n};\n```"},{"question":". What is the result in the console of running the code shown?","options":[{"text":"Storm()","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"'rain'","correct":false},{"text":"'snow'","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nvar Storm = function () {};\nStorm.prototype.precip = 'rain';\nvar WinterStorm = function () {};\nWinterStorm.prototype = new Storm();\nWinterStorm.prototype.precip = 'snow';\nvar bob = new WinterStorm();\nconsole.log(bob.precip);\n```"},{"question":". You need to match a time value such as 12:00:32. Which of the following regular expressions would work for your code?","options":[{"text":"/[0-9]{2,}:[0-9]{2,}:[0-9]{2,}/","correct":false},{"text":"/\\d\\d:\\d\\d:\\d\\d/","correct":true},{"text":"/[0-9]+:[0-9]+:[0-9]+/","correct":false},{"text":"/ : : /","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result in the console of running this code?","options":[{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"window","correct":false},{"text":"{desc: \"logger\"}","correct":true},{"text":"function","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\n'use strict';\nfunction logThis() {\n  this.desc = 'logger';\n  console.log(this);\n}\nnew logThis();\n```"},{"question":". How would you reference the text 'avenue' in the code shown?","options":[{"text":"roadTypes.2","correct":false},{"text":"roadTypes\\[3\\]","correct":false},{"text":"roadTypes.3","correct":false},{"text":"roadTypes\\[2\\]","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nlet roadTypes = ['street', 'road', 'avenue', 'circle'];\n```"},{"question":". What is the result of running this statement?","options":[{"text":"'float'","correct":false},{"text":"'value'","correct":false},{"text":"'number'","correct":true},{"text":"'integer'","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconsole.log(typeof 42);\n```"},{"question":". Which property references the DOM object that dispatched an event?","options":[{"text":"self","correct":false},{"text":"object","correct":false},{"text":"target","correct":true},{"text":"source","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You're adding error handling to the code shown. Which code would you include within the if statement to specify an error message?","options":[{"text":"exception('One or both parameters are not numbers')","correct":false},{"text":"catch('One or both parameters are not numbers')","correct":false},{"text":"error('One or both parameters are not numbers')","correct":false},{"text":"throw('One or both parameters are not numbers')","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nfunction addNumbers(x, y) {\n  if (isNaN(x) || isNaN(y)) {\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". Which method converts JSON data to a JavaScript object?","options":[{"text":"JSON.fromString();","correct":false},{"text":"JSON.parse()","correct":true},{"text":"JSON.toObject()","correct":false},{"text":"JSON.stringify()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When would you use a conditional statement?","options":[{"text":"When you want to reuse a set of statements multiple times.","correct":false},{"text":"When you want your code to choose between multiple options.","correct":true},{"text":"When you want to group data together.","correct":false},{"text":"When you want to loop through a group of statement.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What would be the result in the console of running this code?","options":[{"text":"12345","correct":false},{"text":"1234","correct":false},{"text":"01234","correct":true},{"text":"012345","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nfor (var i = 0; i < 5; i++) {\n  console.log(i);\n}\n```"},{"question":". Which Object method returns an iterable that can be used to iterate over the properties of an object?","options":[{"text":"Object.get()","correct":false},{"text":"Object.loop()","correct":false},{"text":"Object.each()","correct":false},{"text":"Object.keys()","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". After the following code, what is the value of a.length?","options":[],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What will be logged to the console?","options":[{"text":"101","correct":true},{"text":"3","correct":false},{"text":"4","correct":false},{"text":"100","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nvar a = ['dog', 'cat', 'hen'];\na[100] = 'fox';\nconsole.log(a.length);\n```"},{"question":". What is one difference between collections created with Map and collections created with Object?","options":[{"text":"You can iterate over values in a Map in their insertion order.","correct":false},{"text":"You can count the records in a Map with a single method call.","correct":true},{"text":"Keys in Maps can be strings.","correct":false},{"text":"You can access values in a Map without iterating over the whole collection.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the value of dessert.type after executing this code?","options":[{"text":"pie","correct":false},{"text":"The code will throw an error.","correct":false},{"text":"pudding","correct":true},{"text":"undefined","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nconst dessert = { type: 'pie' };\ndessert.type = 'pudding';\n```"},{"question":". 0 && hi","options":[{"text":"ReferenceError","correct":false},{"text":"True","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":true},{"text":"false","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of the following operators can be used to do a short-circuit evaluation?","options":[{"text":"\\++","correct":false},{"text":"\\--","correct":false},{"text":"\\==","correct":false},{"text":"\\|\\|","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement sets the Person constructor as the parent of the Student constructor in the prototype chain?","options":[{"text":"Student.parent = Person;","correct":false},{"text":"Student.prototype = new Person();","correct":true},{"text":"Student.prototype = Person;","correct":false},{"text":"Student.prototype = Person();","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why would you include a \"use strict\" statement in a JavaScript file?","options":[{"text":"to tell parsers to interpret your JavaScript syntax loosely","correct":false},{"text":"to tell parsers to enforce all JavaScript syntax rules when processing your code","correct":true},{"text":"to instruct the browser to automatically fix any errors it finds in the code","correct":false},{"text":"to enable ES6 features in your code","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Variable-defining keyword allows its variable to be accessed (as undefined) before the line that defines it?","options":[{"text":"all of them","correct":false},{"text":"const","correct":false},{"text":"var","correct":true},{"text":"let","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of the following values is not a Boolean false?","options":[{"text":"Boolean(0)","correct":false},{"text":"Boolean(\"\")","correct":false},{"text":"Boolean(NaN)","correct":false},{"text":"Boolean(\"false\")","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of the following is not a keyword in JavaScript?","options":[{"text":"this","correct":false},{"text":"catch","correct":false},{"text":"function","correct":false},{"text":"array","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which variable is an implicit parameter for every function in JavaScript?","options":[{"text":"Arguments","correct":true},{"text":"args","correct":false},{"text":"argsArray","correct":false},{"text":"argumentsList","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". For the following class, how do you get the value of 42 from an instance of X?","options":[{"text":"x.get('Y')","correct":false},{"text":"x.Y","correct":true},{"text":"x.Y()","correct":false},{"text":"x.get().Y","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nclass X {\n  get Y() {\n    return 42;\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". What is the result of running this code?","options":[{"text":"30, ReferenceError, 30, -10","correct":false},{"text":"30, ReferenceError","correct":true},{"text":"30, -10","correct":false},{"text":"ReferenceError, -10","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nsum(10, 20);\ndiff(10, 20);\nfunction sum(x, y) {\n  return x + y;\n}\nlet diff = function (x, y) {\n  return x - y;\n};\n```"},{"question":". Why is it usually better to work with Objects instead of Arrays to store a collection of records?","options":[{"text":"Objects are more efficient in terms of storage.","correct":false},{"text":"Adding a record to an object is significantly faster than pushing a record into an array.","correct":false},{"text":"Most operations involve looking up a record, and objects can do that better than arrays.","correct":true},{"text":"Working with objects makes the code more readable.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement is true about the \"async\" attribute for the HTML script tag?","options":[{"text":"It can be used for both internal and external JavaScript code.","correct":false},{"text":"It can be used only for internal JavaScript code.","correct":false},{"text":"It can be used only for internal or external JavaScript code that exports a promise.","correct":false},{"text":"It can be used only for external JavaScript code.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How do you import the lodash library making it top-level Api available as the \"\\_\" variable?","options":[{"text":"import \\_ from 'lodash';","correct":true},{"text":"import 'lodash' as \\_;","correct":false},{"text":"import '\\_' from 'lodash;","correct":false},{"text":"import lodash as \\_ from 'lodash';","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the following expression evaluate to?","options":[{"text":"True","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"[]","correct":false},{"text":"False","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\n[] == [];\n```"},{"question":". What is the name of a function whose execution can be suspended and resumed at a later point?","options":[{"text":"Generator function","correct":true},{"text":"Arrow function","correct":false},{"text":"Async/ Await function","correct":false},{"text":"Promise function","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What will this code print?","options":[{"text":"2","correct":false},{"text":"1","correct":true},{"text":"Nothing - this code will throw an error.","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nvar v = 1;\nvar f1 = function () {\n  console.log(v);\n};\nvar f2 = function () {\n  var v = 2;\n  f1();\n};\nf2();\n```"},{"question":". Which statement is true about Functional Programming?","options":[{"text":"Every object in the program has to be a function.","correct":false},{"text":"Code is grouped with the state it modifies.","correct":false},{"text":"Date fields and methods are kept in units.","correct":false},{"text":"Side effects are not allowed.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Your code is producing the error: TypeError: Cannot read property 'reduce' of undefined. What does that mean?","options":[{"text":"You are calling a method named reduce on an object that's declared but has no value.","correct":false},{"text":"You are calling a method named reduce on an object that does not exist.","correct":true},{"text":"You are calling a method named reduce on an empty array.","correct":false},{"text":"You are calling a method named reduce on an object that's has a null value.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How many prototype objects are in the chain for the following array?","options":[{"text":"3","correct":false},{"text":"2","correct":true},{"text":"0","correct":false},{"text":"1","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice is _not_ a unary operator?","options":[{"text":"typeof","correct":false},{"text":"delete","correct":false},{"text":"instanceof","correct":true},{"text":"void","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What type of scope does the end variable have in the code shown?","options":[{"text":"conditional","correct":false},{"text":"block","correct":true},{"text":"global","correct":false},{"text":"function","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nvar start = 1;\nif (start === 1) {\n  let end = 2;\n}\n```"},{"question":". What will the value of y be in this code:","options":[{"text":"One","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"TRUE","correct":false},{"text":"Two","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nconst x = 6 % 2;\nconst y = x ? 'One' : 'Two';\n```"},{"question":". Which keyword is used to create an error?","options":[{"text":"throw","correct":true},{"text":"exception","correct":false},{"text":"catch","correct":false},{"text":"error","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What's one difference between the async and defer attributes of the HTML script tag?","options":[{"text":"The defer attribute can work synchronously.","correct":false},{"text":"The defer attribute works only with generators.","correct":false},{"text":"The defer attribute works only with promises.","correct":false},{"text":"The defer attribute will asynchronously load the scripts in order.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The following program has a problem. What is it?","options":[{"text":"The condition in the ternary is using the assignment operator.","correct":true},{"text":"You can't define a variable without initializing it.","correct":false},{"text":"You can't use a ternary in the right-hand side of an assignment operator.","correct":false},{"text":"The code is using the deprecated var keyword.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nvar a;\nvar b = (a = 3) ? true : false;\n```"},{"question":". Which statement references the DOM node created by the code shown?","options":[{"text":"`Document.querySelector('class.pull')`","correct":false},{"text":"`document.querySelector('.pull');`","correct":true},{"text":"`Document.querySelector('pull')`","correct":false},{"text":"`Document.querySelector('#pull')`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```html\n<p class=\"pull\">lorem ipsum</p>\n```"},{"question":". What value does this code return?","options":[{"text":"10","correct":true},{"text":"true","correct":false},{"text":"false","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nlet answer = true;\nif (answer === false) {\n  return 0;\n} else {\n  return 10;\n}\n```"},{"question":". What is the result in the console of running the code shown?","options":[{"text":"10","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":false},{"text":"ReferenceError","correct":true},{"text":"undefined","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nvar start = 1;\nfunction setEnd() {\n  var end = 10;\n}\nsetEnd();\nconsole.log(end);\n```"},{"question":". What will this code log in the console?","options":[{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"\"hello\"","correct":false},{"text":"an object with a constructor property","correct":true},{"text":"an error message","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nfunction sayHello() {\n  console.log('hello');\n}\nconsole.log(sayHello.prototype);\n```"},{"question":". Which collection object allows unique value to be inserted only once?","options":[{"text":"Object","correct":false},{"text":"Set","correct":true},{"text":"Array","correct":false},{"text":"Map","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What two values will this code print?","options":[{"text":"1 then 1","correct":false},{"text":"1 then undefined","correct":false},{"text":"undefined the undefined","correct":true},{"text":"undefined the 1","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```js\nfunction printA() {\n  console.log(answer);\n  var answer = 1;\n}\nprintA();\nprintA();\n```"},{"question":". How does the `forEach()` method differ from a `for` statement?","options":[{"text":"forEach allows you to specify your own iterator, whereas for does not.","correct":false},{"text":"forEach can be used only with strings, whereas for can be used with additional data types.","correct":false},{"text":"forEach can be used only with an array, whereas for can be used with additional data types.","correct":true},{"text":"for loops can be nested; whereas forEach loops cannot.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What will be logged to the console?","options":[{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"function","correct":false},{"text":"windows","correct":false},{"text":"{desc: \"logger\"}","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n'use strict';\nfunction logThis() {\n  this.desc = 'logger';\n  console.log(this);\n}\nnew logThis();\n```"},{"question":". Which choice is an incorrect way to define an arrow function that returns an empty object?","options":[{"text":"=> ({})","correct":false},{"text":"=> {}","correct":true},{"text":"=> { return {};}","correct":false},{"text":"=> (({}))","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why might you choose to make your code asynchronous?","options":[{"text":"to start tasks that might take some time without blocking subsequent tasks from executing immediately","correct":false},{"text":"to ensure that tasks further down in your code are not initiated until earlier tasks have completed","correct":true},{"text":"to make your code faster","correct":false},{"text":"to ensure that the call stack maintains a LIFO (Last in, First Out) structure","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which expression evaluates to true?","options":[{"text":"`[3] == [3]`","correct":false},{"text":"`3 == '3'`","correct":true},{"text":"`3 != '3'`","correct":false},{"text":"`3 === '3'`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of these is a valid variable name?","options":[{"text":"5thItem","correct":false},{"text":"firstName","correct":true},{"text":"grand total","correct":false},{"text":"function","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which method cancels event default behavior?","options":[{"text":"cancel()","correct":false},{"text":"stop()","correct":false},{"text":"preventDefault()","correct":true},{"text":"prevent()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which method do you use to attach one DOM node to another?","options":[{"text":"attachNode()","correct":false},{"text":"getNode()","correct":false},{"text":"querySelector()","correct":false},{"text":"appendChild()","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement is used to skip iteration of the loop?","options":[{"text":"break","correct":false},{"text":"pass","correct":false},{"text":"skip","correct":false},{"text":"continue","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice is valid example for an arrow function?","options":[{"text":"(a,b) => c","correct":true},{"text":"a, b => {return c;}","correct":false},{"text":"a, b => c","correct":false},{"text":"{ a, b } => c","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which concept is defined as a template that can be used to generate different objects that share some shape and/or behavior?","options":[{"text":"class","correct":true},{"text":"generator function","correct":false},{"text":"map","correct":false},{"text":"proxy","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How do you add a comment to JavaScript code?","options":[{"text":"`! This is a comment`","correct":false},{"text":"`# This is a comment`","correct":false},{"text":"`\\\\ This is a comment`","correct":false},{"text":"`// This is a comment`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you attempt to call a value as a function but the value is not a function, what kind of error would you get?","options":[{"text":"TypeError","correct":true},{"text":"SystemError","correct":false},{"text":"SyntaxError","correct":false},{"text":"LogicError","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which method is called automatically when an object is initialized?","options":[{"text":"create()","correct":false},{"text":"new()","correct":false},{"text":"constructor()","correct":true},{"text":"init()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result of running the statement shown?","options":[{"text":"4","correct":false},{"text":"10","correct":false},{"text":"6","correct":true},{"text":"5","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nlet a = 5;\nconsole.log(++a);\n```"},{"question":". You've written the event listener shown below for a form button, but each time you click the button, the page reloads. Which statement would stop this from happening?","options":[{"text":"e.blockReload();","correct":false},{"text":"button.preventDefault();","correct":false},{"text":"button.blockReload();","correct":false},{"text":"e.preventDefault();","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nbutton.addEventListener(\n  'click',\n  function (e) {\n    button.className = 'clicked';\n  },\n  false,\n);\n```"},{"question":". Which statement represents the starting code converted to an IIFE?","options":[{"text":"`function() { console.log('lorem ipsum'); }()();`","correct":false},{"text":"`function() { console.log('lorem ipsum'); }();`","correct":false},{"text":"`(function() { console.log('lorem ipsum'); })();`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement selects all img elements in the DOM tree?","options":[{"text":"`Document.querySelector('img')`","correct":false},{"text":"`Document.querySelectorAll('<img>')`","correct":false},{"text":"`Document.querySelectorAll('img')`","correct":true},{"text":"`Document.querySelector('<img>')`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why would you choose an asynchronous structure for your code?","options":[{"text":"To use ES6 syntax","correct":false},{"text":"To start tasks that might take some time without blocking subsequent tasks from executing immediately","correct":false},{"text":"To ensure that parsers enforce all JavaScript syntax rules when processing your code","correct":false},{"text":"To ensure that tasks further down in your code aren't initiated until earlier tasks have completed","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the HTTP verb to request the contents of an existing resource?","options":[{"text":"DELETE","correct":false},{"text":"GET","correct":true},{"text":"PATCH","correct":false},{"text":"POST","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which event is fired on a text field within a form when a user tabs to it, or clicks or touches it?","options":[{"text":"focus","correct":true},{"text":"blur","correct":false},{"text":"hover","correct":false},{"text":"enter","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result in the console of running this code?","options":[{"text":"function","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false},{"text":"Function.prototype","correct":false},{"text":"window","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfunction logThis() {\n  console.log(this);\n}\nlogThis();\n```"},{"question":". Which class-based component is equivalent to this function component?","options":[{"text":"`class Greeting extends React.Component { render() { return <h1>Hello {this.props.name}!</h1>; } }`","correct":true},{"text":"`class Greeting extends React.Component { constructor() { return <h1>Hello {this.props.name}!</h1>; } }`","correct":false},{"text":"`class Greeting extends React.Component { <h>Hello {this.props.name}!</h>; } }`","correct":false},{"text":"`class Greeting extends React.Component { render({ name }) { return <h1>Hello {name}!</h1>; } }`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst Greeting = ({ name }) => <h1>Hello {name}!</h1>;\n```"},{"question":". Which class-based lifecycle method would be called at the same time as this effect Hook?","options":[{"text":"componentWillUnmount","correct":false},{"text":"componentDidUpdate","correct":false},{"text":"render","correct":false},{"text":"componentDidMount","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nuseEffect(() => {\n  // do things\n}, []);\n```"},{"question":". What is the output of this code?","options":[{"text":"ReferenceError: obj is not defined","correct":false},{"text":"{}","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":true},{"text":"null","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nvar obj;\nconsole.log(obj);\n```"},{"question":". How would you use the TaxCalculator to determine the amount of tax on \\$50?","options":[{"text":"calculate(50);","correct":false},{"text":"new TaxCalculator().calculate(\\$50);","correct":false},{"text":"TaxCalculator.calculate(50);","correct":true},{"text":"new TaxCalculator().calculate(50);","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nclass TaxCalculator {\n  static calculate(total) {\n    return total * 0.05;\n  }\n}\n```"}]